http://www.westtoronto.org/wp/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - West Toronto Church of God
Questions?
Sunday Services – COVID-19 Response
Workers Recruitment (Volunteer)
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This Policy provides information on how we use personal information collected on this site. We encourage you to read it carefully before submitting any personal data.
By using the site, you are accepting the terms of this privacy policy which are subject to change at any time.  Changes will be posted and will only apply to activities and information on a go forward basis. You are encouraged to review this policy whenever you visit the site to ensure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: The practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personal information like names,  residential addresses, email addresses etc. This information is submitted on a voluntary basis by our visitors and is used only to fulfill their specific request, unless they provide permission to use it in another manner. eg. to add to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these organizations for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personal information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
1655 Wilson Avenue, North York, Ontario, Canada, M3L 1A5Phone: 1(416) 235-1333
Do NOT follow this link or you will be banned from the site!
COVID-19 Re-entry GuidelinesREAD MORE
+
